Édgar Díez Alonso

Final year Software Engineering student Academic year 2021/2022

edgardiez7@gmail.com +34 644588381

in www.linkedin.com/in/edgardiezalonso

https://github.com/Edgardiez7/CV-Projects.git



Career Objective

Motivated, teamwork-oriented, and responsible final year Software Engineering student with the goal of keep developing the skills acquired at university.

Specializing in Data Science through personal projects consisting in acquiring, cleaning, interpreting and visualizing data.

Education

Degree in Software Engineering - Universidad de Valladolid (2018-2022)

Final year student, academic year 2021/2022.

Every subject from previous years is passed.

Degree in Medicine - Universidad Autónoma de Madrid (2014-2018)

Studied for four years. Changed degree due to lack of vocation.

Science and Technology High School Certificate (2012-2014)

With High Honors and "Extraordinary High School Award" (only awarded to 1 person in my city every year).

Professional Experience

Developer and Bug Tester. AzerothCore (Oct 2021 – Dec 2021)

Developer and Bug Tester for an OpenSource non-profit MMO development platform.

Programming and Robotics tutor. PlayCodeAcademy (July 2021 – August 2021)

Taught programming, 3D design, and drone programming to high school students.

Private tutoring (Sept 2018- Sept 2021)

Teaching Math, Physics and Chemistry to High School students.

Certifications and achievements

- Data Analysis, Cleaning and Visualization with Python, Kaggle (2021)
- Data Analysis with Python Certificacion, FreeCodeCamp (2021)
- Scientific Computing with Python Certification, FreeCodeCamp (2021)
- High Honors and Extraordinary High School Award studies in High School (2014)
- Winner of the Physics Olympics, universitary district of Valladolid (2014)
- First Aid and Lifeguarding course (2013)
- "Aldea Internacional Seattle" Scholarship, Fundación Española de la Lengua (2011)

Languages

- Spanish. Native language.
- English. B2 Official Language School.
- German. B1 Official Language School.

Skills

- Python, Java, C, HMTL, CSS, JS, SQL Server.
- Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn.
- Angular + Spring Boot.
- Software design, development and testing.
- Linux / Unix.